<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Todoist on Rajath Ramakrishna</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/todoist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Todoist on Rajath Ramakrishna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:32:14 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/todoist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OpenClaw use case: research assistant with Todoist</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/openclaw-use-case-research-assistant-with-todoist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:32:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/openclaw-use-case-research-assistant-with-todoist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to use OpenClaw to automate some of the tasks I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenClaw is great for acting as a research assistant and I configured it to do the research for some of the tasks I have in my Todoist. Whenever I think of capturing a task, I do it in Todoist and get to it later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To automate research tasks like comparing headphones, or summarizing a the comment thread of a HackerNews post, I asked the bot to create a cron job every 4 hours and do the research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now every 6 hours it checks Todoist and looks for tasks with the label &lt;code&gt;ellie&lt;/code&gt; (the name of my bot) and picks up the task. It does all the research and puts what it finds in a markdown file in a specific directory. It also adds additional metadata, if any, at the end of the file. Once it does all that, it notifies me on Discord with a brief summary of what it did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this, my Todoist workflow hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed at all. I still add tasks to Todoist, except I add a label to some of the tasks. The rest is handled by OpenClaw cron job. Once it notifies me on Discord about the task completion, I can ask it to mark the task as complete in Todoist, and it does that for me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
