<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weeknotes on Rajath Ramakrishna</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/weeknotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weeknotes on Rajath Ramakrishna</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:09:44 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/weeknotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week Notes - 26-06</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/week-notes---26-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:09:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/week-notes---26-06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week I was quite busy with work, but I did play around with &lt;a href=&#34;https://openclaw.io&#34;&gt;OpenClaw&lt;/a&gt; a bit more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;explorations&#34;&gt;Explorations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I installed &lt;a href=&#34;https://tailscale.com&#34;&gt;Tailscale&lt;/a&gt; on all my devices. I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing a blog post about it soon. The setup was way easier than I thought it would be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I augmented my &lt;a href=&#34;https://todoist.com&#34;&gt;Todoist&lt;/a&gt; grocery helper workflow on OpenClaw to make it check for deals/coupons on QFC as it adds each item to my Todoist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OpenClaw by default uses Raspberry Pi as its coding agent and when I asked it to build a couple of web apps, it did an okay job. I had to prompt it a bunch of times to fix some minor UI bugs and it really struggled with it. So, I used &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/anthropics/claude-code&#34;&gt;claude-code&lt;/a&gt; to rewrite one of the web apps and make enhancements (and fix bugs) in the other web app. I also made sure to use the frontend-design plugin to get a polished and professional looking UI. It did an awesome job and I was really happy with the result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;projects&#34;&gt;Projects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Worked on an Android app that I&amp;rsquo;m calling Bloggo which is to write markdown files from the phone and push it to GitHub. This is mainly to blog on the go and not have to depend on a laptop and run git commands in order to post something to Hugo (or a similar static site generator). I&amp;rsquo;ll be writing a more detailed blog post about this soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;misc&#34;&gt;Misc&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t get much reading done. I was kinda caught up with perfecting my set up with OpenClaw and Tailscale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blog-posts-i-wrote&#34;&gt;Blog posts I wrote&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/openclaw-use-case-add-groceries-to-todoist&#34;&gt;OpenClaw use case: add groceries to Todoist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/openclaw-use-case-improvement-to-todoist-grocery-helper&#34;&gt;OpenClaw use case: improvement to Todoist grocery helper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week Notes - 26-05</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/week-notes---26-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:23:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/week-notes---26-05/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was quite an interesting and productive week. Here are some of the things I did:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;projects&#34;&gt;Projects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I vibe-coded an Android app called &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rrajath/expander&#34;&gt;Expander&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s a text expansion app that works for both static and dynamic snippets (like date, time, day, with custom formats).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also vibe-coded an emacs package called &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rrajath/org-retro-journal&#34;&gt;org-retro-journal.el&lt;/a&gt; which is like Memories in Google Photos but for journaling. You can look back at what you did that exact day or the nearest date each year across your journal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;explorations&#34;&gt;Explorations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I installed &lt;a href=&#34;https://openclaw.ai&#34;&gt;OpenClaw&lt;/a&gt; on my Raspberry Pi and created some automations. It acts as a research assistant where it scans my todoist tasks every few hours and does the research, outputting the analysis to a markdown file and letting me know on discord that it completed the task (along with a short summary of what it did)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blog-posts-i-wrote&#34;&gt;Blog posts I wrote&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/org-retro-journal&#34;&gt;org-retro-journal: an emacs package for looking back through your journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/moving-from-github-pages-to-cloudflare-pages&#34;&gt;Moving from GitHub Pages to Cloudflare Pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/openclaw-adventures&#34;&gt;OpenClaw adventures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/expander-an-android-app-for-text-expansion&#34;&gt;Expander - an Android app for text expansion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/openclaw-use-case-research-assistant-with-todoist/&#34;&gt;OpenClaw use case: research assistant with Todoist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week Notes - 26-04</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/week-notes-26-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:05:17 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/week-notes-26-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s everything I did last week&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fediverse-stuff&#34;&gt;Fediverse stuff&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stumbled upon &lt;a href=&#34;https://home.omg.lol/&#34;&gt;omg.lol&lt;/a&gt; and found it really interesting. After a few minutes of checking out the services that were offered, I joined and created a &lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.omg.lol/&#34;&gt;profile page&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.omg.lol/now&#34;&gt;now page&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.weblog.lol/&#34;&gt;weblog&lt;/a&gt;. I also joined &lt;a href=&#34;https://social.lol/home&#34;&gt;social.lol&lt;/a&gt; and it has some of the nicest people there. I&amp;rsquo;m really digging this whole ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;domain-registrar-switch&#34;&gt;Domain registrar switch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realized I was paying a little too much for my domain at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.namecheap.com/&#34;&gt;Namecheap&lt;/a&gt;. And they kept increasing their prices. Found out about &lt;a href=&#34;https://porkbun.com/&#34;&gt;porkbun&lt;/a&gt; and saw some good reviews by the fine folks at social.lol and ended up switching. The whole migration took about 15 minutes and it was really smooth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blog-posts-i-wrote&#34;&gt;Blog posts I wrote&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/posts/app-defaults-2025/&#34;&gt;App Defaults - 2025 Edition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;projects&#34;&gt;Projects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Made an enhancement to &lt;a href=&#34;https://rrajath.com/&#34;&gt;my blog&lt;/a&gt; hosted on GitHub pages. The search box was huge and had a white background. It was looking ugly when the blog had a dark theme. With the help of LLM, I updated the CSS so that the search box blends with the blog theme and it now looks much nicer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
